

Assistant BPS

Permanent Address: H. No 916, Ward 2, Raj Mohalla,

Sonipat - 131001

Current Address: WZ 78, Dayal Sar Road, Uttam

Nagar West, New Delhi - 110059

Phone: (+91) 9953681108

Email: Mukhi.nikhil1991@gmail.com

Professional Summary

Dedicated Support Associate with 4+ years of experience in different domain like US Mortgage, UK Customer Service and Insurance Operations. Recognized for my ability to communicate with customers, provide exceptional service. MBA focused in field of HR and Finance

Work Experience

DXC Technologies, Noida Assistant BPS, May 2019 – Sep 2021

- Working on CRM system
- Conducting customer satisfaction surveys to understand what areas of company's services needs improvement
- Catering to customer chat inquiries
- Query resolution
- Dealing with customer issues and handling customer concerns
- Interacting with customers to ensure they have a desirable experience

BT Global Services Pvt Ltd, Gurugram Associate, Nov 2016 – Aug 2017

- Managing large amounts of chat enquiries from the customer in a timely manner
- Identifying customers' needs, clarify information, research every issue and providing solutions
- Dealing with customer issues and handling customer concerns
- Following "scripts when handling" different issues
- Interacting with customers to ensure they have a desirable experience
- Adhering to company's rules and regulations

Quatrro Mortgage Solutions Pvt Ltd, Gurugram Associate, April 2015 – May 2016

- Handle customer enquiry over chat in a timely and friendly manner.
- Evaluate problems and complaints of the customers and provide proper solutions to them.
- Respond to the needs of customers and provide service
- Supporting the customer through a ticketing system
- Providing detailed information to customers
- Following up with the customers for any further information

Education

DCRUST University, Murthal, Sonipat (Haryana) (2012 - 2014)

MBA (HR & Finance)

M.D.U, Rohtak (Haryana) (2009 - 2012)

BBA

H.V.P Sr Sec School, Sonipat (Haryana) (2008 - 2009)

XII (Commerce)

Key Skills

- Time Management
- Work Ethics
- · Team Player
- Effective Communication Skills
- Organization & Prioritization

Extra Curricular Activities

- Secured 2nd position in Business Quiz in Techno-Management Fest
- Secured 3rd position in District Level Taekwondo Championship
- Secured 3rd Position in Inter college Cricket tournament held at PM College of Engineering, Sonipat
- Participated at North Zone Taekwondo Championship held at Amritsar

Declaration

I, hereby declare that all the information furnished above is true to the best of my knowledge

Date: Place: (Nikhil Mukhi)